... O-oh, my head gasket.
哦…我的颈部垫圈！
Eh... what the?
啊 这什么鬼地方？
The Cons' warship?
虎子的战舰？
Ratchet? Don't ask how I got here. Long story.
救护车 别问我怎么来的…说来话长
Ratchet? You copy?
救护车？听到了吗？
Oh scrap!
噢 见鬼
Stealthy... stealthy...
悄悄地过去 打枪地不要…
Starscream?
红蜘蛛？
Why is it that every time I return to my old stomping grounds
为什么每次我回到我的旧基地
I find an Autobot roaming the halls?
都能发现有汽车人在大厅里闲逛！
Don't tell me you came crawling back to Megatron.
别告诉我你爬回来找威震天了
Hardly. Now out of my way.
不可能！别挡路！
Scream. You've got to show me the way off this boat.
小红 你得告诉我离开这里的路
Sorry, too busy.
对不起 没时间！
Look. When you needed help...
别忘了 上次你落难的时候…
As I recall, we bartered.
我记得 我们是公平交易
So, unless you have anything of value to offer me,
所以 除非你能提供回报
step aside!
否则一边去！
The exit. Now!
立马告诉我出口！
I may have given Arcee a free pass when she and I last met!
虽然上次我放过了阿尔茜
But I won't hesitate to skewer you as I did a certain Cliffjumper!
但我也可以毫不迟疑地刺穿你 就像对飞过山一样
Perish, Bulkhead!
去死吧 隔板！
This is for Cliffjumper! For Bumblebee! For everything.
这是为了飞过山！为了大黄蜂！为了你所做的一切！
You left me no choice...
这是你逼我的…
Argh! What I would not give to have wings again!
我愿不惜一切代价再次飞起来…
Just as I left it.
啊… 跟我离开时一样
The Harbinger. Things are finally looking up.
先驱号的事情终于有了转机
Oh really!? Not one scrap of energon!
噢 真的假的？！一丁点能量残渣都不剩？
A laboratory.
一个实验室？
And it's functional.
并且还能运作…
Protoforms?
原生体…
Bulkhead to base. Picked up a strong reading.
隔板呼叫基地 发现一个很强的信号
I'm going to check it out.
我去调查清楚
Let's see... Transference of binary bonding, submolecular infusion, hmm...
让我们看看 分子内二价键连接
The formula seems straightforward enough.
这个方程式很容易弄懂
Well, my little lambs of clay, you look like alright for the molding.
好了 我的粘土小人儿 看来你们已经准备好塑形了…
Let's give cloning a whirl, shall we?
…我们来个快速克隆 怎么样？
No sight of activity.
没有活动的迹象
Hahahahaha...
哈哈哈哈…
Give me a light!
…赐予我生命吧！
Like-minded company... at last.
啊…同志们…终于找到组织了…
Energon? Boxed and ready for pickup?
能量体…打包待运？
... Scrap!
糟了！
Esteemed members of my armada!
我亲爱的成员们
You now stand upon the very precipice of glory
你们即将见证
to meet the destiny which I have so tenaciously worked toward.
我长久以来不懈追求的光荣时刻
Dynamic leadership of the Decepticons!
霸天虎的领导权应该轮流坐庄！
I am... delighted to hear that we are on the same page, heh.
我…很高兴咱们达成了共识 呵呵
We are as one, Commander.
我们是一体的 指挥官
We share your memories.
我们分享你的记忆
Your very feelings.
你的切身感受
Even your insatiable quest for power.
甚至你对权力无尽的渴求!
I see.
我知道了
Fortunately, The Harbinger's tracking systems
很幸运 先驱号的追踪系统还能
have remained synced with Megatron's warship.
追踪到威震天的飞船
Of course, we shall require a means of reaching the...
当然我们要先想个办法登上去
Oh! You can transform!?
啊？你们能变形？
... Of course you can!
你们当然能变形！
How else would you fly to the ship.
否则怎么飞到飞船上去？
That was a test which you all... eh... passed.
我只是想考验一下 你们都通过了
Now take flight and snuff Megatron's accursed Spark!
现在飞过去熄灭威震天那被诅咒的火种！
... O-oh, my head gasket.
哦…我的颈部垫圈！
Spread out. Keep to the shadows.
散开 保持隐蔽
Any one of us is an instant target aboard this warship.
我们中任何一人被发现都会立刻受到攻击的
But to be seen together would sacrifice the element of surprise.
但要是被看到我们在一起 就没有奇袭效果了
Whoever manages to find Megatron first, report your position!
无论是谁先找到了威震天 报告你的位置
Starscream?
红蜘蛛？
I cannot wait to savour the vivid details of Megatron's demise...
我迫不及待地等着欣赏威震天死亡的场面
Ah!
啊
What is happening?!
到底怎么回事？
This is for Cliffjumper! For Bumblebee! For everything.
这是为了飞过山！为大黄蜂！为了你所做的一切！
Ahhhhh...
啊！
My genetic code provides my clones with a T-cog I no longer possess
我的遗传代码给了克隆体们我早已失去的变形齿轮！
and all I get is their agony?
而我得到的竟是他们的痛苦？
A comm unit.
通讯台！
Bulkhead to base. Do you read?
隔板呼叫基地 听到了吗？
Do you copy?
听得到吗？
Halt!
站住！
A Decepticon beacon, at last.
霸天虎信号 终于找到了！
Devoted servants, the time has come.
忠诚的奴仆们 机会终于来了！
For the ultimate retribution.
为复仇而战吧
Optimus, no word yet from Bulkhead.
擎天柱 没有隔板的消息
But I am detecting some rather curious subterranean frequencies.
不过我监测到一些奇怪的地下信号
Of Earthly origin?
地球人的吗？
I do not yet know what they are, but I do know where.
我还不确定是什么 但我知道它的位置
The coordinates at which we last encountered Megatron.
坐标是我们最后遇到威震天的地方…
And Airachnid.
还有毒蜘蛛
And Airachnid's Insecticon.
还有毒蜘蛛的机器昆虫
Arise, my armada. And attack!
出洞吧 我的虫群们 攻击！
We are in all likelihood witnessing the launch of a mission to terminate Megatron.
我们看到的 极有可能是一次针对威震天的刺杀行动
I can't think of a reason to stop that.
我想不出阻止它的理由
Even if we could.
虽然我们做得到
But we can stop Airachnid.
但是我们能阻止毒蜘蛛
Rear guard, engage the Autobots.
后卫部队 向汽车人开火
Stealthy... stealthy...
悄悄地过去 打枪地不要…
Lord Megatron!
威震天陛下
Yes, what is it?
嗯 什么事？
An intruder.
有入侵者！
Autobot?
汽车人？
Starscream. He was last seen in vicinity of the bridge.
是红蜘蛛 刚刚出现在舰桥附近
No!
不！
Underground. There's a surprise.
钻地 还是老把戏
Megatron. It has come time to settle old scores.
威震天…是算旧账的时候了…
Hahahahaha... really, Starscream? All on your own?
哈哈哈哈 是吗 红蜘蛛? 就凭你一个人？
Actually...
事实上…
Clones. Well-played, Starscream.
克隆 干得不赖啊 红蜘蛛
If you're even here among your underlings.
你可能根本没有跟这些喽罗一起来
Underlings? We are as one.
喽罗？我们是一体的
Though many.
同时也是个军团
Bring me Starscream's head on a stick.
把红蜘蛛的脑袋带给我
And I will reward you as my Second-in-command. All of you.
我就让你们都当我的副官
No! You're trying to trick us!
不 你在骗我们！
Am I?
有吗？
Is he?
是吧?
Accept my proposal and we all win.
采纳我的提议 我们都会是赢家
Otherwise, you will merely end up terminating each other to get the spoils.
否则你们只会死于抢夺战利品的争斗之中
It is your nature, after all.
毕竟那是你们的天性…
Don't listen to him!
别听他的！
Prepare to perish at my hand!
准备死在我手上吧！
Our hands!
我们的手上！
Yes! Only our combined firepower will assure Megatron's destruction.
没错 只有我们集中火力才能确保威震天被消灭
Take aim!
准备！
Do you hear that?
你们听到了吗？
Ignore! Fire on three!
别管它 数到3就开火！
One. Two!
1 2
What was that?
刚才是什么声音？
The sound of the tables turning.
翻盘的声音
What is going on up there?
那上面发生了什么？
Exterminating you was so gratifying the first three times!
前三次摧毁你还是很惬意的
Airachnid. A busy day for assassins.
毒蜘蛛？刺客们今天赶集吗？
Arcee!
阿尔茜
When you extinguish my Spark, make it hurt.
当你熄灭我火种的时候 做得痛苦点
You know: I would extend the courtesy to you.
你知道我会对你下更重的手
I'm not like you.
我可不像你
Very well.
很好…
No!
不！
Forgive us, one true Lord and Master.
原谅我们 真正的主人
This day has certainly seen its share of thwarted intentions.
今天南辕北辙的事真是够多了
One way or another, I'm getting off this boat!
无论如何 我都要离开这艘破船！
Now what?!
又怎么了！
Out of my way!
好狗不挡道！
My Liege! Our power core has been compromised.
我的君王 我们的动力设备被破坏了
Prepare for landing.
准备着陆…
Stasis. She deserves worse.
休眠状态 便宜她了
I intended worse. More times than you know.
我的原计划可不会这么温柔 你想象不到的
You are stronger for the choice you made.
你的这一选择 会让你变得更为强大
Guys, you're not gonna believe the day I had!
伙计们 你们绝对想不到我这一天的经历！
You too, huh?
你也是 嗯？
Lord Starscream! Your most loyal servant has returned.
红蜘蛛陛下 您最忠实的仆人回来了
But I regret to inform you that our collective mission has failed.
但我很遗憾地通知您 我们的任务失败了
Hmm, yes. I got that sense.
嗯 没错 我感觉到了
Something to do with a throbbing ache in my side!
因为我疼得苦不堪言
You... knew I would attempt to terminate you...
你知道我要杀了你？
Ah... I feel your pain. Really I do.
我感受到了你的痛苦 真的
Arrrgh! Scrap that hurt!
啊！见鬼 好疼呀！